Guide to the Duke Forest Records, 1931-ongoing UA.10.09.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2019.0079, circa 1930s-1950s
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 22, Comp 40, 41, 49 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 23, Comp 42, 47, 48 (plus new area) (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 24, Comp 43, 44, 45, 46 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 25, Comp 50, 55, 56, 57 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 26, Comp 51 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 1, Compartment 1 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 2, Compartment 2, 3 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 34, Comp 71, 79, 80, 81 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 3, Compartment 4 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 4, Compartment 5 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 5, Compartment 6, 9, 10 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 6, Compartment 8, 7 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 7, Compartment 11, 14 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 8, Comp 12, 13 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 9, Comp 15 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 10, Comp 16 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 11, Comp 17 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 35, Comp 72, 77 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 36, Comp 74, 75 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 37, Comp 76, 78 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 31, Comp 66, 67, 73 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 28, Comp 58, 59, 60 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 29, Comp 61, 62 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 12, Comp 18, 36, 37 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 13, Comp 19, 20 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 33, Comp 69, 70 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 30, Comp 63, 64, 65 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 27, Comp 53, 54 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Index to Sheets (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Sheet 32, Comp 68 (Box 102)
  - Durham Division Soil Survey Study - Small Sheets, Clayton Tract, Don Paschall Tract, R. E. Paschall Tract, Kinsman Tract, Neal Tract (Box 102)
  - Arboretum: Arboretum Plantings (Box 102)
  - Arboretum Summary by Type, Age Class, and Stand (Box 102)
  - Soil Survey Procedure of Soil Survey of the Durham Division of Duke Forest (Box 102)
  - Soil Analysis - Duke Forest 1954 - 1959 (Box 102)
  - Plantation Studies: Plantation Measurements (Box 102)
  - Plantation Summaries (Box 102)
  - Planting Plans 1941 (Box 102)
  - Planting Plans 1942-43, 1942-1943 (Box 102)
  - Compartment 15, Stand 1, Plantation 2 - New Hope Creek Division, Duke Forest (Box 102)
  - Erosion Control (Box 102)
  - Silvicultural Experiments: Mechanical Thinning Operation Using a Bulldozer - Comp 41, Stand 8, Durham Division (Box 102)
  - Honeysuckle Control Experiment - Hines Tract, Blackwood Division (Box 102)
  - Girdling and Poisoning - Erwin Cotton Mills Tract (1949) (Box 102)
  - Report on "Ammating" in Stand 1, Comp 61 and Stand 7, Comp 62 - Durham Division (Box 102)
  - Twig and Bud Pruning (Box 102)
  - Korstian C-29 Std 3 Annosus Damage (Box 102)
  - Patch Cutting Experiment: 1946- Clear Cutting in Patches Comp. 56 Field Data Patches 4, 6 and 12, 1940s-1950s (Box 102)
  - Cleaning Clear Cut Patches 1956 (Box 102)
  - Clear Cutting in Patches Comp. 56 Gate 3, 1956 (Box 102)
  - Trenching Experiment: Notes on Trenching Study (Box 102)
  - Trenched Plot and Boyoucos Block Experiment Comp 63, Durham Division, Duke Forest (Box 102)
  - Trenched Plot Moisture Differences (Box 102)
  - Trenching Study (Box 102)
  - T. S. Data (Folder 1 - Trenching study data dealing with all of the trenched and control milacres but not used in final report) (Box 102)
  - Trenching Study Photographs and data from which drawn and legend explanation of project (Box 102)
  - Trenching Study (Box 102)
  - Norm Christensens's Research: Nutrient Data (Box 102)
  - Pattern Program (Box 102)
  - Soil Collections (Box 102)
  - Lieth Paper on Xeric Sand ridges (Box 102)
  - Misc. Forest Notes (Box 102)
  - Misc. For. Notes (Box 102)
  - Taxonomic Considerations (Box 102)
  - Bormann Plot Spp. Codes (Box 102)
  - Corrections to PSP Data 9/85 Bob Knox (Box 102)
  - Christensen and MacAllen Graphs, Etc. (Box 102)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P65-77 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P78-90 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P91-103 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P104-116 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P117-129 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records CP144 and CP117 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P200-206, P300-305 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P1-13 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P14-26 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study CP23-26 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study CP27-31 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P27-39 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P40, 41, 42;Pond Pine Soil Site Study P65-77 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P78-90 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P91-103 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P104-116 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P117-129 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study CP117 and CP144 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P200-206, P300-305 (Box 103)
  - Stand 4, Comp. 19, New Hope Creek;Stand 2, Comp. 19, New Hope Creek (Box 103)
  - Stand 7, Comp. 19, New Hope Creek (Box 103)
  - Upland loblolly (Box 103)
  - Slash Pine Field Records CP235, S1-13 (Box 103)
  - Slash Pine Field Records S14-26 (Box 103)
  - Unlabled folders (4) (Box 103)
  - Duke Forest Management Maps (Box 103)
  - Arboretum Summary by Type, Age Class, and Stand (Box 103)
  - Soil Survey Procedure of Soil Survey of the Durham Division of Duke Forest (Box 103)
  - Soil Analysis - Duke Forest 1954 - 1959 (Box 103)
  - Plantation Studies: Plantation Measurements (Box 103)
  - Plantation Summaries (Box 103)
  - Planting Plans 1941 (Box 103)
  - Planting Plans 1942 and 43 (Box 103)
  - Compartment 15, Stand 1, Plantation 2 - New Hope Creek Division, Duke Forest (Box 103)
  - Erosion Control (Box 103)
  - Silvicultural Experiments: Mechanical Thinning Operation Using a Bulldozer - Comp 41, Stand 8, Durham Division (Box 103)
  - Honeysuckle Control Experiment - Hines Tract, Blackwood Division (Box 103)
  - Girdling and Poisoning - Erwin Cotton Mills Tract (1949) (Box 103)
  - Report on "Ammating" in Stand 1, Comp 61 and Stand 7, Comp 62 - Durham Division (Box 103)
  - Twig and Bud Pruning (Box 103)
  - Korstian C-29 Std 3 Annosus Damage (Box 103)
  - Patch Cutting Experiment:1946- Clear Cutting in Patches Comp. 56 Field Data Patches 4, 6 and 12 (Box 103)
  - Cleaning Clear Cut Patches 1956 (Box 103)
  - Clear Cutting in Patches Comp. 56 Gate 3 (Box 103)
  - Trenching Experiment: Notes on Trenching Study (Box 103)
  - Trenched Plot and Boyoucos Block Experiment Comp 63, Durham Division, Duke Forest (Box 103)
  - Trenched Plot Moisture Differences (Box 103)
  - Trenching Study (Box 103)
  - T. S. Data (Folder 1 - Trenching study data dealing with all of the trenched and control milacres but not used in final report) (Box 103)
  - Trenching Study Photographs and data from which drawn and legend explanation of project (Folder 2) (Box 103)
  - Trenching Study (Box 103)
  - Norm Christensens's Research: Nutrient Data (Box 103)
  - Pattern Program (Box 103)
  - Soil Collections (Box 103)
  - Lieth Paper on Xeric Sand ridges (Box 103)
  - Misc. Forest Notes (Box 103)
  - Misc. For. Notes (Box 103)
  - Taxonomic Considerations (Box 103)
  - Bormann Plot Spp. Codes (Box 103)
  - Corrections to PSP Data 9/85 Bob Knox (Box 103)
  - Christensen and MacAllen Graphs, Etc. (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P65-77 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P78-90 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P91-103 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P104-116 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P117-129 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records CP144 and CP117 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Field Records P200-206, P300-305 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P1-13 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P14-26 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study CP23-26 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study CP27-31 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P27-39 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P40, 41, 42 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P65-77 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P78-90 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P91-103 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P104-116 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P117-129 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study CP117 and CP144 (Box 103)
  - Pond Pine Soil Site Study P200-206, P300-305 (Box 103)
  - Stand 4, Comp. 19, New Hope Creek (Box 103)
  - Stand 2, Comp. 19, New Hope Creek (Box 103)
  - Stand 7, Comp. 19, New Hope Creek (Box 103)
  - Upland loblolly (Box 103)
  - Slash Pine Field Records CP235, S1-13 (Box 103)
  - Slash Pine Field Records S14-26 (Box 103)
  - Unlabled folders (4) (Box 103)
  - Duke Forest Management Maps (Box 103)